onmanga.com 2009-06-04

# Privacy Policy | ON Networks

## ON Networks Privacy Policy

**ON Networks, Inc.** ("ON Networks") recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others (collectively or individually "Users") who use [www.onnetworks.com](http://www.onnetworks.com/) or other web sites owned or operated by ON Networks (collectively the "Website") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Website.

  * Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the ON Networks Terms of Use.
  * Please note that any comment or other content you post or send to the Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

### 1\. Information Collection and Use

**_General_**

  * ON Networks does not require that you register in order to view its programming. Registration is required to use certain interactive features such as posting comments, participating in user forums, and in order to receive notices about shows.
  * ON Networks collects personal information when you register with ON Networks, when you visit Website, when you sign up to receive notices of upcoming shows, when you enter promotions or sweepstakes, or any time you provide information to ON Networks about yourself. ON Networks may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, and other personally-identifying information ("Personal Information"). When you register with ON Networks and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * ON Networks automatically receives and records other non-personally-identifying information ("Non-Personal Information") on our server logs from your browser even if you do not register with ON Networks, for example, your IP address, ON Networks cookie information, and the page you visit.
  * ON Networks uses Non-Personal Information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**_Children_**

  * No part of the ON Networks website is directed at persons under 13\. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access OnNetwork at any time or in any manner.
  * ON Networks does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age.
  * If ON Networks learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on ON Networks without verified parental consent, then ON Networks will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

### 2\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * ON Networks does not rent, sell, or share Personal Information with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with ON Networks under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your Personal Information to help ON Networks communicate with you about offers from ON Networks and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We provide Non-Personal Information to interested third-parties for purposes of understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Website.
  * We use both your Personal Information and certain Non-Personal Information to improve the quality and design of the Website and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.
  * We may share Personal Information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other forms of legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We may share Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ON Networks. terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We may transmit Personal Information if ON Networks is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, ON Networks will notify active known users if there is a need to change this Privacy Policy based on an ON Networks acquisition or merger.
  * In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.
  * Keep in mind that any personal information, or comments that you voluntarily disclose on the Website, for example on video viewing pages, or on discussion boards, becomes publicly available. Either your account name or your real name (your choice) is displayed to other Users when you send messages through the Website.

### 3\. Advertising

  * ON Networks utilizes a variety of techniques to display targeted advertisements to users, including the use by ON Networks of both Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.
  * ON Networks may utilize the third party advertisers or ad serving companies to display targeted advertisements to users, but ON Networks does not provide any Personal Information to any third party advertisers.

### 4\. Cookies 

  * ON Networks may set and access ON Networks cookies on your computer. You may disable these cookies within your browser, but some portions of the Website may require that your ON Networks cookies be enabled.
  * ON Networks lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies. use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to ON Networks' cookies. To learn more about cookies visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

### 5\. Confidentiality and Security

  * ON Networks uses commercially reasonable technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any Personal Information you transmit to ON Networks and you do so at your own risk.
  * We limit access to Personal Information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with Personal Information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

### 6\. Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information 

  * You can edit your ON Networks account information at any time by visiting your account profile page.
  * We reserve the right to use your Personal Information in order to send you certain communications relating to the ON Networks service, such as service announcements, and administrative messages, that are considered part of your ON Networks account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
  * You can deactivate your ON Networks account by editing your account profile.

### 7\. International Users

  * If you are a User accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy as incorporated in our Terms of Use, you will be transferring your Personal Information into the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

### 8\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

  * ON Networks may update this policy at any time in its sole discretion and without prior notice. We will strive to notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your ON Networks account and/or by placing a notice on the Website.

### 9\. Effective Date

  * This Privacy Policy was last modified March 7, 2007.

### 10\. Contact Information

  * If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:

ON Networks, Inc.  
504 Lavaca St.  
Suite 960  
Austin, TX 78701  
info@onnetworks.com

**BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE WEBSITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL MEAN THAT YOU ACCEPT THOSE CHANGES.**
